I see the warning on the console screen
You're pulling harder than I've ever seen
I'm caught inside the gravity well A one-way
ticket on a carousel The navigation is totally
blind I'm leaving all the safety behind
Structural integrity is starting to bend I'm
accelerating faster to the bitter end You're a
massive body, I'm a satellite I'm breaking into
pieces in the dead of night We crossed the road's
limit Tearing me apart. Tearing me apart.
We crossed the roach limit. A fatal attraction.
A heavy heart that's still surviving when you
get this close. A total system failure. A lethal
dose. Yeah, we crossed the roach limit.
The telemetry spinning into the red.
I should've listened to the things they said But
the magnetic field is pulling me in I feel the
friction underneath my skin I'm caught in the
orbit of a dangerous star The structural
integrity is starting to bend I'm accelerating
faster to the bitter end You're a massive body,
I'm a satellite I'm breaking into pieces in the
dead of night We crossed the roach limit Tearing
me apart Tearing me apart
WE CROSS THE ROACH LIMIT A FATAL ATTRACTION A
HEAVY HEART THERE'S NO SURVIVING WHEN YOU GET
THIS CLOSE A TOTAL SYSTEM FAILURE A LETHAL DOSE
YEAH WE CROSS THE ROACH LIMIT
We crossed the roach limit Tearing me apart,
tearing me apart
We crossed the roach limit A fatal attraction, a
heavy heart There's no surviving when you get
this close A total system failure, a lethal dose
Yeah, we crossed the road's limit. Tearing me
apart.
System Failure!